'use strict';

const STORE = [

// Questions, answers, and correctanswer inside of an array  
// JSON objects need to have "" on both key and value pair
  {
  "question":"1. Which of the following games was the first US game to utilize battery backup instead of a password?",
  "answers":["Super Mario Bros", "Excitebike", "The Legend of Zelda", "Metroid"],
  "correctAnswer": "The Legend of Zelda"
  },
  {
    "question":"2. Which of these games is a horizontally scrolling shooter?",
    "answers":["Galaga", "Gradius", "StarTropics", "Bubble Bobble"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gradius"
  },
  {
    "question":"3. Which of these games allowed you to create your own levels?",
    "answers":["Excitebike", "Ice Climber", "PAC-Man", "Super Mario Bros. 2"],
    "correctAnswer": "Excitebike"
  },
  {
    "question":"4. Mario made a cameo appearance in which of the following games?",
    "answers":["Tecmo Bowl", "Tetris", "Ghosts 'n Goblins", "Punch-Out!!"],
    "correctAnswer": "Punch-Out!!"
  },
  {
    "question":"5. Which of these NES Classics was published last?",
    "answers":["Super Contra", "Kirby's Adventure", "StarTropics", "Double Dragon II: The Revenge"],
    "correctAnswer": "Kirby's Adventure"
  },
  {
    "question":"6. Which Mega Man II boss uses the Time Stopper weapon?",
    "answers":["Metal Man", "Flash Man", "Quick Man", "Air Man"],
    "correctAnswer": "Flash Man"
  },
  {
    "question":"7. Which Punch-Out!! character cannot get back up once knocked down?",
    "answers":["Glass Joe", "King Hippo", "Von Kaiser", "Bald Bull"],
    "correctAnswer": "King Hippo"
  },
  {
    "question":"8. Which of these games starred a female character?",
    "answers":["Metroid", "Ninja Gaiden", "Donkey Kong Jr.", "Castlevania"],
    "correctAnswer": "Metroid"
  },
  {
    "question":"9. What is the proper combination to exit the Lost Woods in The Legend of Zelda?",
    "answers":["North East West South", "South North West East", "East West North South", "North West South West"],
    "correctAnswer": "North West South West"
  },
  {
    "question":"10. What is the starting weapon of Mike, the main character of StarTropics?",
    "answers":["BB Gun", "Baseball Bat", "Hammer", "Yo-Yo"],
    "correctAnswer": "Yo-Yo"
  }
  ];


